

Ahmed Gul

Date of birth: 01/01/1997 | Nationality: Afghan | Gender: Male |

Phone number: (+92) 03155389640 (Mobile) | Email address:

ahmadgul969@gmail.com | Facebook:

https://www.facebook.com/ahmadgul.ahmadgul.31 | LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ahmed-gul-41086a194

Whatsapp Messenger: 03155389640

Address: Mansehra, KPK Pakistan, 21300, Mansehra, Pakistan (Home)

ABOUT ME

My name is Ahmed Gul. I am 25 years old. I done my Bachelor Degree from Hazara University. I am web developer. I am not a lazy person at all and I prefer talking to other confident people. I think i am considerate and trustworthy. I always do my work on time.

WORK EXPERIENCE

05/05/2021 - 04/01/2022 Mansehra, Pakistan

WEB DEVELOPER DPO OFFICE

Working as web Developer Maintaining DPO Office website

18/12/2022 - 30/06/2023 Peshawar, Pakistan

WEB APPLICATION DEVELOPER PIXEL E-SERVICES

Full Stack Web Developer

Department Software House | **Email** <u>pixeleservicesofficial@gmail.com</u> | **Website** <u>www.pixeleservices.com</u>

10/07/2023 – 15/09/2023 Mansehra, Pakistan

WEB DEVELOPER TENSAIDEV

Frond Web Developer

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

01/03/2013 - 01/04/2015 Mansehra, Pakistan

MATRIX Tameer-E-millat Hazara Public School and College

Address Shinkiari Mansehra KPK Pakistan, 21300, Mansehra, Pakistan

31/05/2015 - 02/06/2017 Mansehra, Pakistan

FSC Tameer-E-millat Hazara Public School and College

Address Shinkiari Mansehra KPK Pakistan, 21300, Mansehra, Pakistan

BACHELOR DEGREE Hazara University

Web Development

Address Dhodial Mansehra, KPK, Pakistan, 21300, Mansehra, Pakistan | Field of study Computer Science |

Final grade 3.82 CGPA | Thesis Online FIR Management System

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): **PASHTO**

Other language(s):

	UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
	Listening	Reading	Spoken production	Spoken interaction	
ENGLISH	B2	B2	B2	B2	C1
URDU	C1	C2	C2	C1	C1

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

DIGITAL SKILLS

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

PROJECTS

04/05/2021 - 03/01/2022

Online FIR Management System

31/12/2022 - 20/01/2023

Point of Sales and Expense Tracker

15/07/2023 - 30/07/2023

Record Change Request Management System (RCRMS) A Record Change Request Management System is developed for university. it's help student to request change a Name, D.O.B or Father name that is incorrect.

HONOURS AND AWARDS

01/01/2022

Gold Medal - Hazara University Got highest GPA in BS degree in Computer Science

HOBBIES AND INTERESTS

Reading

Playing Cricket

Traveling

Programming